So in today's video we will talk about
ICC Bank Limited, so
friends, the share of this bank,
its current price here is ₹939 which is the
last closing and friends, if we talk about
its returns, then
friends, the return you got in five days,
you have seen a negative 0.94
here, along with this, if
we talk about the growth or what DR has been received here in the last 1 month, then
friends, if you check it in one month, then
you have seen a growth of 0.02% here,
if we also see its growth here for the last 6 months, then
friends, the
growth that has happened here within 6 months,
you have seen a return of 0.9% here, so along with this, if
we look at its return for one year, then
friends, if we look at its return in one year, then
friends,
here you have seen a return of 36% here in the
last one year, so
friends, here if we look at its return in one year  Here, after
looking at the previous starting price,
its starting price was 6800,
in 2022,
its answer is closing price, the current price,
friends, you are seeing it is ₹939, right now you will get its
current price here and at the same time,
if we see its five-year
return, then friends, you will be surprised to see the return seen in 5 years, so
friends,
you have seen a return of 225% for 5 years here, so
friends, if we
see its history here, its starting price,
5 years ago, was ₹282 and today
its price here has become ₹939, so friends, to get
updates of such Sher, friends, now
you must subscribe to our channel and
like the video, Bhole, thank you, very
match
[Sangeet]